Babatunde Samson Odewole

odewoletundesamson@gmail.com



+2347039831390



linkedin.com/in/babatunde-samson-o-360878187 & https://github.com/Tundesamson26



Summary

Self-driven software developer and designer with a highly creative mind. I'm available for entry/junior role(it could be remote or relocation). Problem-solving experience with HTML, CSS ,Javascript, python, PHP, Laravel and WordPress.....I love to learn new skills and knowledge, also Love diversity because it's my desire to expose to new cultures. You can learn more about what I do in Github link attached above

Experience



Software Developer

BIGSAM PROJECTS AND DESIGNS

Mar 2019 - Present (1 year 10 months +)

Graphic Designer

BigSam Innovation

Jun 2012 - Present (8 years 7 months +)

Software Engineer

BIGSAM PROJECTS AND DESIGNS

Jun 2019 - Nov 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Education



FCAH&PT

National Diploma, Agriculture, Agriculture Operations, and Related Sciences 2016 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



Programming Foundations: Databases - LinkedIn

Programming Foundations: Fundamentals - LinkedIn

Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End - LinkedIn

Skills

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • HTML5 • Python (Programming Language) • Graphic Design • Git • GitHub • PHP • Laravel • Vue.js